2020s count to hit us real hard and show
you which they was not ready but we
can't really help it can be 20/20 has
been a series of lockdown lockdown one
people looking first ascensions most of
us wanted groceries flour sugar salt
milk eggs knocked out two men then even
looking slightly more different kind of
essentials probably gadgets
a-15 doctor three also gave us a
separate list of essentials could be a
different kind of a mom probably some
kind of a cleaning gadget so a
definition of essentials kept changing
through the spirit of that but remember
that being financially healthy is also
an essential and the key to being
financially healthy is to have healthy
savings savings is an essential but it's
actually pretty confusing for most of us
we don't anymore better begin saving how
to go about it and especially in these
times when the economy is crashing stock
markets of the time fortunately some
jobs are being lost it becomes very very
understand what goes behind savings how
does one go about to help you understand
all of this and to break the jargon and
confusion and the difficulties around
understanding products such as for your
management what is portfolio management
usual funds stock markets equity
investing banking insurance all of that
we are going to bring series of webinars
industry
trust me these people are the best you
can find take advice on investing on
sales so don't forget to register for
this essential course on why and how
saving is essential
it's an essential all of us need in our
lives to be financially healthy so
remember to register for this course as
clear tax brings you the best in the
class
to help you leave a happy and healthy
financial see you now
[Music]